targetix.net 2019-04-16

# Privacy Policy | hybrid.ai | hybrid.ai

Effective: January 1, 2018

We have prepared this Privacy Notice to explain how, why, and when we collect data from you to provide targeted advertising services for our clients.

Please note that this Privacy Notice does not apply to data that we collect when you visit the Hybrid Adtech’s website at hybrid.ai. To learn what data we collect when you visit our website, please scroll down to Hybrid Adtech Website Privacy Notice.

1\. About Hybrid Adtech's Services 

  * Hybrid Adtech provides targeted advertising services for our advertiser clients ("Advertisers"). When you visit a website operated by an Advertiser or a third party site where we could serve an ad to you, we may collect some or all of the data described in the Hybrid Adtech Service Privacy Notice. Our platform uses that data as well as other data described below to help Advertisers provide ads to you that are more relevant to you.
  * For example, if you visit an Advertiser's website and shop for a dress, our Platform (or another platform we work with) may later serve you with targeted ads for the Advertiser’s brand of dresses as you browse the internet or through other channels, such as mobile apps.

2\. What data we collect and how we use it 

  * We may collect the following categories of information for the purposes explained below.

  * Advertiser website activity: This is data about your browsing activity on the Advertiser's website. For example, which pages you visited and when, and what items you placed into your online shopping cart.
  * Device and browser information: This is technical information about the device or browser you use to access the Advertiser's website. For example, your device's IP address, cookie string data and (in the case of mobile devices) your device type and mobile device's unique identifier such as the Apple IDFA or Android Advertising ID. 
  * Ad data: This is data about the online ads we have served (or attempted to serve) to you. It includes things like how many times an ad has been served to you, what page the ad appeared on, and whether you clicked on or otherwise interacted with the ad. 
  * Data from Advertising Partners: This is data that we receive from other digital advertising companies that we work with (“Advertising Partners”) to help us deliver ads to you and recognize you across browsers and devices. This may include pseudonymous advertiser identifiers that some Advertisers or other third party ad platforms choose to share with us, such as your "Customer ID" with an Advertiser. We may work with these Advertising Partners to synchronize their unique, anonymous identifiers to our own to enhance data points about a particular unique browser or device. 
  * We use this data to help our Advertisers identify and serve ads to you that are more relevant to you. We also use this data to operate, improve and enhance our services including enhancing the data points we or our Advertising Partners have about a particular user, browser, or device, or to target, optimize, cap, or synchronize advertising. 

4\. Cookies and related technologies 

  * The Hybrid Adtech platform uses cookies, tracking pixels and related technologies to provide our services for Advertisers. Cookies are small data files that are served by our platform and stored on your device. They enable us to identify your device when you move between different websites and applications, so that we can serve targeted advertising to you. 
  * Specifically, the Hybrid Adtech cookie we serve through the Hybrid Adtech platform for this purpose is named “vid”. We may also drop an additional Hybrid Adtech opt-out (“optOut”) cookie if you opt-out as described below. We may also drop cookies from our Advertising Partners for the purposes described above. The Advertising Partner cookies dropped vary by Advertiser implementation. 

5\. Your choices and opting-out 

  * We recognize how important your online privacy is to you, so we offer the following options for controlling the targeted ads you receive and how we use your data: 

  * You can opt out of receiving targeted ads served by us or on our behalf by clicking on the blue icon that typically appears in the corner of the ads we serve or by clicking on the opt-out button at the bottom of this document. Please note that, if you delete your cookies or upgrade your browser after having opted out, you will need to opt out again. If you opt-out we may collect some data about your online activity for operational purposes (such as fraud prevention) but it won't be used by us for the purpose of targeting ads to you.
  * While we may link multiple browsers or devices to you, if you opt out on a device or browser we will not use data collected after you opted out on that device or browser for targeted advertising purposes. Therefore, if you use multiple browsers or devices you will need to execute this opt out on each browser or device. 
  * To opt out of receiving targeted ads that are based on your behavior across different mobile applications follow the below instructions, for iOS and Android devices: 
    * iOS 7 or Higher: Go to your Settings > Select Privacy > Select Advertising > Enable the “Limit Ad Tracking” setting
    * For Android devices with OS 2.2 or higher and Google Play Services version 4.0 or higher: Open your Google Settings app > Ads > Enable “Opt out of interest-based advertising”

  * Opting out will not prevent you from seeing ads, but those ads will likely be less relevant because they won’t be tailored to your interests. The ads might, for instance, be randomly generated or based on the web page you are visiting.
  * Some internet browsers allow users to send a "Do Not Track" signal to websites they visit. We do not respond to this signal.
  * In addition, if you are located in the European Economic Area you may also have the right to access, correct or update some of the information we hold about you. You can also request that we delete your information. If you wish to exercise any of these rights, please contact us at [support@hybrid.ai](mailto:support@hybrid.ai). Please note that in many cases, we hold identifiable information only on behalf of our Advertiser clients, and we may instead direct you to contact them.

8\. International transfers

  * We may transfer the information we collect about you to countries other than the country where we originally collected it for the purposes of storage and processing of data and operating our services. Those countries may not have the same data protection laws as your country. However, when we transfer your information to other countries, we will protect that information as described in this Privacy Notice and take steps, where necessary, to ensure that international transfers comply with applicable laws. For example, if we transfer your information from the European Economic Area to a country outside it, such as the United States, we will seek to take additional steps such as entering into EU compliant data transfer agreements with the data importer where necessary.

9\. Changes to this Privacy Notice 

  * Changes to this Privacy Notice will be posted on this page. If we make a material change to our privacy practices, we will provide notice on the site or by other means as appropriate.

10\. Contact us about questions or concerns

  * If you have any questions about this Privacy Notice or our privacy practices, you can contact [support@hybrid.ai](mailto:support@hybrid.ai).
  * If you are located in the European Economic Area and we are processing your data as a data controller, Hybrid Adtech Inc. is the data controller of your information. To contact Hybrid Adtech Inc. please email [support@hybrid.ai](mailto:support@hybrid.ai) or write to us at the following address:
  * Hybrid Adtech, Inc.
  * 616 Corporate way suite 2-3353   
Valley Cottage, NY 10989, USA 
  * +1 (646) 883 5777

## Hybrid Adtech Website Privacy Policy

Effective: January 1, 2018

We have prepared this Privacy Notice to explain how, why, and when we collect data from you on our website.

Please note that this Privacy Notice only applies to data that we collect when you visit the Hybrid Adtech website at hybrid.ai.

1\. About Hybrid Adtech's Services 

  * Hybrid Adtech provides targeted advertising services for our advertiser clients ("Advertisers"). When you visit a website operated by an Advertiser or a third party site where we could serve an ad to you, we may collect some or all of the data described in the Hybrid Adtech Service Privacy Notice above. Our platform uses that data as well as other data described below to help Advertisers provide ads to you that are more relevant to you.
  * For example, if you visit an Advertiser's website and shop for running shoes, our Platform (or another platform we work with) may later serve you with targeted ads for the Advertiser’s brand of running shoes as you browse the internet or through other channels, such as emails.

2\. What data we collect and how we use it 

  * We may collect the following categories of information on our website and use them for the purposes explained below.

  * Website activity: Data about your browsing activity on our website
  * Device and browser information: Technical information about the device or browser you use to access our website. For example, your device's IP address, and (in the case of mobile devices) your device type and mobile device's unique identifier such as the Apple IDFA or Android Advertising ID.
  * Contact Information: If you choose to provide your name, email address or phone number
  * Account Information: If you open a account, we will collect your username and a password and other information to necessary to open and access your account
  * Customer Service Information: Information you may provide to customer service including survey responses
  * Financial Information: Credit card number or other payment account information. This information is collected directly by our payments processor and not stored at Hybrid Adtech.
  * Third party information: We may collect additional information about you from third party sources where we have the rights to do so.

  * We use this data to:

  * provide Hybrid Adtech services and customer support
  * collect fees and troubleshoot problems
  * prevent potential fraud and enforce our Terms of Service
  * customize, measure, and improve our website and services
  * deliver targeted marketing to you
  * contact you by email or phone about your account or our services including to market our services to you

4\. Cookies and related technologies 

  * The Hybrid Adtech website uses cookies, tracking pixels and related technologies. Cookies are small data files that are served by our platform and stored on your device. Our site uses cookies dropped by us or third parties for a variety of purposes including to operate and personalize the website. Also, cookies may also be used to track how you use the site to target ads to you on other websites.
  * To get more information about the individual cookies dropped by our website, please see the Adjust Ad Preferences link on the footer of our website.

5\. Your choices and opting-out 

  * We recognize how important your online privacy is to you, so we offer the following options for controlling the targeted ads you receive and how we use your data:

  * You can opt-out of receiving targeted ads served by us: You can opt out of receiving targeted ads served by us or on our behalf by clicking on the by clicking on the opt-out button at the bottom of this page. Please note that, if you delete your cookies or upgrade your browser after having opted out, you will need to opt out again. Further, if you use multiple browsers or devices you will need to execute this opt out on each browser or device. If you opt-out we may collect some data about your online activity for operational purposes (such as fraud prevention) but it won't be used by us for the purpose of targeting ads to you.

  * Some internet browsers allow users to send a "Do Not Track" signal to websites they visit. We do not respond to this signal.
  * In addition, if you are located in the European Economic Area you may also have the right to access, correct or update some of the information we hold about you. You can also request that we delete your information. If you wish to exercise any of these rights, please contact us at [support@hybrid.ai](mailto:support@hybrid.ai).

8\. International transfers 

  * We may transfer the information we collect about you to countries other than the country where we originally collected it for the purposes of storage and processing of data and operating our services. Those countries may not have the same data protection laws as your country. However, when we transfer your information to other countries, we will protect that information as described in this Privacy Notice and take steps, where necessary, to ensure that international transfers comply with applicable laws. For example, if we transfer your information from the European Economic Area to a country outside it, such as the United States, we will seek to take additional steps such as entering into EU compliant data transfer agreements with the data importer where necessary.

9\. Changes to this Privacy Notice

  * Changes to this Privacy Notice will be posted on this page. If we make a material change to our privacy practices, we will provide notice on the site or by other means as appropriate.

10\. Contact us about questions or concerns 

  * If you have any questions about this Privacy Notice, our privacy practices, or with Hybrid Adtech generally, you can contact [support@hybrid.ai](mailto:support@hybrid.ai).
  * If you are located in the European Economic Area and we are processing your data as a data controller, Hybrid Adtech Inc. is the data controller of your PII. To contact Hybrid Adtech Inc. please email [support@hybrid.ai](mailto:support@hybrid.ai) or write to us at the following address:
  * Hybrid Adtech, Inc.
  * 616 Corporate way suite 2-3353   
Valley Cottage, NY 10989, USA 
  * +1 (646) 883 5777
